var DICTIONARIES = ["Alphabet", "Third Grade", "KIIP1"];

var alphabet = [
  {id: "1", question: "A", answer: "a"},
  {id: "2", question: "B", answer: "b"},
  {id: "3", question: "C", answer: "c"},
  {id: "4", question: "D", answer: "d"},
  {id: "5", question: "E", answer: "e"},
  {id: "6", question: "F", answer: "f"},
  {id: "7", question: "G", answer: "g"},
  {id: "8", question: "H", answer: "h"},
  {id: "9", question: "I", answer: "i"},
  {id: "10", question: "J", answer: "j"},
  {id: "11", question: "K", answer: "k"},
  {id: "12", question: "L", answer: "l"},
  {id: "13", question: "M", answer: "m"},
  {id: "14", question: "N", answer: "n"},
  {id: "15", question: "O", answer: "o"},
  {id: "16", question: "P", answer: "p"},
  {id: "17", question: "Q", answer: "q"},
  {id: "18", question: "R", answer: "r"},
  {id: "19", question: "S", answer: "s"},
  {id: "20", question: "T", answer: "t"},
  {id: "21", question: "U", answer: "u"},
  {id: "22", question: "V", answer: "v"},
  {id: "23", question: "W", answer: "w"},
  {id: "24", question: "X", answer: "x"},
  {id: "25", question: "Y", answer: "y"},
  {id: "26", question: "Z", answer: "z"},
];

var thirdGrade = [
  {id: "1", question: "a", answer: "한 개의"},
  {id: "2", question: "about", answer: "~에 대해"},
  {id: "3", question: "an", answer: "한 개의"},
  {id: "4", question: "and", answer: "~과, ~랑"},
  {id: "5", question: "ant", answer: "개미"},
  {id: "6", question: "apple", answer: "사과"},
  {id: "7", question: "ball", answer: "공"},
  {id: "8", question: "bat", answer: "방망이"},
  {id: "9", question: "be", answer: "~이다"},
  {id: "10", question: "bear", answer: "곰"},
  {id: "11", question: "big", answer: "큰"},
  {id: "12", question: "birthday", answer: "생일"},
  {id: "13", question: "black", answer: "검은색"},
  {id: "14", question: "blue", answer: "파란색"},
  {id: "15", question: "book", answer: "책"},
  {id: "16", question: "brown", answer: "갈색"},
  {id: "17", question: "bus", answer: "버스"},
  {id: "18", question: "bye", answer: "잘가"},
  {id: "19", question: "cake", answer: "케이크"},
  {id: "20", question: "can", answer: "할 수 있다"},
  {id: "21", question: "carrot", answer: "당근"},
  {id: "22", question: "cat", answer: "고양이"},
  {id: "23", question: "catch", answer: "~일 잡다"},
  {id: "24", question: "chicken", answer: "치킨"},
  {id: "25", question: "close", answer: "닫다"},
  {id: "26", question: "cloudy", answer: "흐린"},
  {id: "27", question: "cold", answer: "추운"},
  {id: "28", question: "color", answer: "색깔"},
  {id: "30", question: "cookie", answer: "쿠키"},
  {id: "31", question: "crayon", answer: "크레용"},
  {id: "33", question: "cup", answer: "컵"},
  {id: "34", question: "cute", answer: "귀여운"},
  {id: "35", question: "dad", answer: "아빠"},
  {id: "36", question: "dance", answer: "춤을 추다"},
  {id: "37", question: "dog", answer: "개"},
  {id: "38", question: "doll", answer: "인형"},
  {id: "39", question: "dolphin", answer: "돌고래"},
  {id: "40", question: "door", answer: "문"},
  {id: "41", question: "down", answer: "아래로"},
  {id: "42", question: "duck", answer: "오리"},
  {id: "43", question: "egg", answer: "계란"},
  {id: "44", question: "eight", answer: "여덟"},
  {id: "45", question: "eleven", answer: "열하나"},
  {id: "46", question: "eraser", answer: "지우개"},
  {id: "47", question: "everyone", answer: "모두"},
  {id: "48", question: "fast", answer: "빠른"},
  {id: "49", question: "fish", answer: "생선"},
  {id: "50", question: "five", answer: "다섯"},
  {id: "51", question: "fly", answer: "날다"},
  {id: "52", question: "fork", answer: "포크"},
  {id: "53", question: "four", answer: "넷"},
  {id: "54", question: "game", answer: "놀이"},
  {id: "55", question: "glue stick", answer: "풀"},
  {id: "56", question: "go", answer: "가다"},
  {id: "57", question: "good", answer: "좋은"},
  {id: "58", question: "goodbye", answer: "잘가세요"},
  {id: "59", question: "great", answer: "아주 잘있다"},
  {id: "60", question: "green", answer: "초록색"},
  {id: "61", question: "gum", answer: "껌"},
  {id: "62", question: "happy", answer: "기쁜"},
  {id: "63", question: "hat", answer: "모자"},
  {id: "64", question: "have", answer: "가지다"},
  {id: "65", question: "hello", answer: "안녕하세요"},
  {id: "66", question: "here", answer: "여기에"},
  {id: "67", question: "hi", answer: "안녕"},
  {id: "68", question: "hot", answer: "더운"},
  {id: "69", question: "how", answer: "얼마나"},
  {id: "70", question: "I", answer: "나는"},
  {id: "71", question: "in", answer: "~에"},
  {id: "72", question: "ink", answer: "잉크"},
  {id: "73", question: "it", answer: "그것"},
  {id: "74", question: "juice", answer: "주스"},
  {id: "76", question: "jump", answer: "뛰다"},
  {id: "77", question: "key", answer: "열쇠"},
  {id: "78", question: "king", answer: "왕"},
  {id: "79", question: "kiwi", answer: "키위"},
  {id: "80", question: "leg", answer: "다리"},
  {id: "81", question: "lemon", answer: "레몬"},
  {id: "82", question: "let's", answer: "~하자"},
  {id: "83", question: "like", answer: "좋아하다"},
  {id: "84", question: "lip", answer: "입술"},
  {id: "85", question: "long", answer: "긴"},
  {id: "86", question: "look", answer: "바라보다"},
  {id: "87", question: "many", answer: "몇"},
  {id: "88", question: "meet", answer: "만나다"},
  {id: "89", question: "melon", answer: "멜론"},
  {id: "90", question: "milk", answer: "우유"},
  {id: "91", question: "mom", answer: "엄마"},
  {id: "92", question: "net", answer: "그물"},
  {id: "93", question: "nice", answer: "반가운"},
  {id: "94", question: "nine", answer: "아홉"},
  {id: "95", question: "no", answer: "아니다"},
  {id: "96", question: "nose", answer: "코"},
  {id: "97", question: "not", answer: "않다"},
  {id: "98", question: "okay", answer: "괜찮은"},
  {id: "99", question: "old", answer: "나이가 ~인"},
  {id: "100", question: "one", answer: "하나"},
  {id: "101", question: "open", answer: "열다"},
  {id: "102", question: "orange (식품)", answer: "오렌지"},
  {id: "103", question: "orange", answer: "주황색"},
  {id: "105", question: "outside", answer: "밖에"},
  {id: "106", question: "pear", answer: "배"},
  {id: "107", question: "pencil case", answer: "필통"},
  {id: "108", question: "pencil", answer: "연필"},
  {id: "109", question: "pie", answer: "파이"},
  {id: "110", question: "pig", answer: "돼지"},
  {id: "111", question: "pizza", answer: "피자"},
  {id: "112", question: "please", answer: "부디"},
  {id: "113", question: "potato", answer: "감자"},
  {id: "114", question: "queen", answer: "여왕"},
  {id: "115", question: "raining", answer: "비가 오는"},
  {id: "116", question: "red", answer: "빨간색"},
  {id: "117", question: "robot", answer: "로봇"},
  {id: "118", question: "ruler", answer: "자"},
  {id: "119", question: "run", answer: "달리다"},
  {id: "120", question: "sad", answer: "슬픈"},
  {id: "121", question: "scissors", answer: "가위"},
  {id: "122", question: "seven", answer: "일곱"},
  {id: "123", question: "sing", answer: "노래하다"},
  {id: "124", question: "sit down", answer: "앉다"},
  {id: "125", question: "six", answer: "여섯"},
  {id: "126", question: "skate", answer: "스케이트를 타다"},
  {id: "127", question: "small", answer: "작은"},
  {id: "128", question: "snake", answer: "뱀"},
  {id: "129", question: "snowing", answer: "눈이 오는"},
  {id: "130", question: "sorry", answer: "미안한"},
  {id: "131", question: "stand up", answer: "일어나다"},
  {id: "132", question: "sunny", answer: "화창한"},
  {id: "133", question: "swim", answer: "수영하다"},
  {id: "134", question: "t-shirt", answer: "티셔츠"},
  {id: "135", question: "ten", answer: "열"},
  {id: "136", question: "tent", answer: "텐트"},
  {id: "137", question: "thank", answer: "감사"},
  {id: "138", question: "that", answer: "저것"},
  {id: "139", question: "the", answer: "그"},
  {id: "140", question: "this", answer: "이것"},
  {id: "141", question: "three", answer: "셋"},
  {id: "142", question: "to", answer: "~하여"},
  {id: "143", question: "tomato", answer: "토마토"},
  {id: "144", question: "too", answer: "~도 역시"},
  {id: "145", question: "twelve", answer: "열둘"},
  {id: "146", question: "two", answer: "둘"},
  {id: "147", question: "up", answer: "위로"},
  {id: "148", question: "violin", answer: "바이올린"},
  {id: "149", question: "weather", answer: "날씨"},
  {id: "150", question: "welcome", answer: "~해도 좋은"},
  {id: "151", question: "what", answer: "무엇"},
  {id: "152", question: "white", answer: "희색"},
  {id: "153", question: "window", answer: "창문"},
  {id: "154", question: "x-ray", answer: "엑스레이"},
  {id: "155", question: "year", answer: "해"},
  {id: "156", question: "yellow", answer: "노란색"},
  {id: "157", question: "yes", answer: "네, 그래요"},
  {id: "158", question: "you", answer: "너, 너희들"},
  {id: "159", question: "zoo", answer: "동물원"},
];

var KIIP1 = [
  {id: "1", question: "가게", answer: "store"},
  {id: "2", question: "가격", answer: "price"},
  {id: "3", question: "가깝다", answer: "close"},
  {id: "4", question: "가다", answer: "go"},
  {id: "5", question: "가르치다", answer: "teach"},
  {id: "6", question: "가방", answer: "bag"},
  {id: "7", question: "가수", answer: "singer"},
  {id: "8", question: "가스레인지", answer: "gas range"},
  {id: "9", question: "가습기", answer: "humidifier"},
  {id: "10", question: "가운데", answer: "middle"},
  {id: "11", question: "가을", answer: "autumn"},
  {id: "12", question: "가족", answer: "family"},
  {id: "13", question: "가지", answer: "eggplant"},
  {id: "14", question: "가지다", answer: "have"},
  {id: "15", question: "간호사", answer: "nurse"},
  {id: "16", question: "갈비", answer: "rib"},
  {id: "17", question: "갈아타다", answer: "transfer"},
  {id: "18", question: "감", answer: "feeling"},
  {id: "19", question: "감기에 걸리다", answer: "catch a cold"},
  {id: "20", question: "감사합니다", answer: "thank you"},
  {id: "21", question: "감자", answer: "potato"},
  {id: "22", question: "값", answer: "value"},
  {id: "23", question: "강아지", answer: "puppy"},
  {id: "24", question: "개", answer: "dog"},
  {id: "25", question: "개(단위명사)", answer: "thing (counter)"},
  {id: "26", question: "거기", answer: "there"},
  {id: "27", question: "거실", answer: "livingroom"},
  {id: "28", question: "거울", answer: "mirror"},
  {id: "29", question: "건강에 좋다", answer: "it's good for your health"},
  {id: "30", question: "건강하다", answer: "healthy"},
  {id: "31", question: "건축가", answer: "architect"},
  {id: "32", question: "걷다", answer: "walk"},
  {id: "33", question: "걸다", answer: "call (phone)"},
  {id: "34", question: "겨울", answer: "winter"},
  {id: "35", question: "결혼", answer: "marriage"},
  {id: "36", question: "결혼기념일", answer: "wedding anniversary"},
  {id: "37", question: "결혼식", answer: "wedding ceremony"},
  {id: "38", question: "경복궁", answer: "Gyeongbokgung"},
  {id: "39", question: "경주", answer: "Gyeongju"},
  {id: "40", question: "경찰관", answer: "police officer"},
  {id: "41", question: "경찰서", answer: "police station"},
  {id: "42", question: "경험", answer: "experience"},
  {id: "43", question: "계단", answer: "stairs"},
  {id: "44", question: "계란", answer: "egg"},
  {id: "45", question: "계속", answer: "continue"},
  {id: "46", question: "계시다", answer: "be there"},
  {id: "47", question: "계절", answer: "season"},
  {id: "48", question: "고객", answer: "customer"},
  {id: "49", question: "고구마", answer: "sweet potato"},
  {id: "50", question: "고기", answer: "meat"},
  {id: "51", question: "고맙습니다", answer: "thank you"},
  {id: "52", question: "고모", answer: "aunt"},
  {id: "53", question: "고추", answer: "pepper"},
  {id: "54", question: "고프다", answer: "hungry"},
  {id: "55", question: "곳", answer: "place"},
  {id: "56", question: "공공 기관", answer: "public institutions"},
  {id: "57", question: "공기가 좋다", answer: "the air is good"},
  {id: "58", question: "공무원", answer: "official"},
  {id: "59", question: "공부", answer: "study"},
  {id: "60", question: "공부하다", answer: "to study"},
  {id: "61", question: "공연", answer: "show"},
  {id: "62", question: "공원", answer: "park (place)"},
  {id: "63", question: "공장", answer: "factory"},
  {id: "64", question: "공책", answer: "notebook"},
  {id: "65", question: "공항", answer: "airport"},
  {id: "66", question: "과일", answer: "fruit"},
  {id: "67", question: "과자", answer: "snack"},
  {id: "68", question: "과장님", answer: "supervisor"},
  {id: "69", question: "관광", answer: "tourism"},
  {id: "70", question: "괜찮다", answer: "okay"},
  {id: "71", question: "괜찮아요", answer: "it's okay"},
  {id: "72", question: "교사", answer: "teacher"},
  {id: "73", question: "교실", answer: "classroom"},
  {id: "74", question: "교통편", answer: "transportation"},
  {id: "75", question: "구경", answer: "look around"},
  {id: "76", question: "구급상자", answer: "first aid kit"},
  {id: "77", question: "구두", answer: "shoes"},
  {id: "78", question: "구청", answer: "district office"},
  {id: "79", question: "국물", answer: "broth"},
  {id: "80", question: "국수", answer: "noodle"},
  {id: "81", question: "국적", answer: "nationality"},
  {id: "82", question: "군만두", answer: "fried dumplings"},
  {id: "83", question: "군인", answer: "soldier"},
  {id: "84", question: "권", answer: "volume (series)"},
  {id: "85", question: "귀", answer: "ear"},
  {id: "86", question: "귀걸이", answer: "earring"},
  {id: "87", question: "귀엽다", answer: "cute"},
  {id: "88", question: "귤", answer: "tangerine"},
  {id: "89", question: "그네를 타다", answer: "play on the swings"},
  {id: "90", question: "그래서", answer: "therefore"},
  {id: "91", question: "그럼", answer: "then"},
  {id: "92", question: "그릇", answer: "bowl"},
  {id: "93", question: "그리고", answer: "and"},
  {id: "94", question: "그리다", answer: "draw"},
  {id: "95", question: "그림", answer: "drawing"},
  {id: "96", question: "그저께", answer: "day before yesterday"},
  {id: "97", question: "극장", answer: "theater"},
  {id: "98", question: "근처", answer: "near by"},
  {id: "99", question: "금요일", answer: "Friday"},
  {id: "100", question: "기념일", answer: "anniversary"},
  {id: "101", question: "기다리다", answer: "wait"},
  {id: "102", question: "기대되다", answer: "be expected"},
  {id: "103", question: "기분", answer: "feeling"},
  {id: "104", question: "기쁘다", answer: "happy"},
  {id: "105", question: "기술자", answer: "technician"},
  {id: "106", question: "기운", answer: "strength"},
  {id: "107", question: "기자", answer: "reporter"},
  {id: "108", question: "기차", answer: "train"},
  {id: "109", question: "기차역", answer: "train station"},
  {id: "110", question: "기침", answer: "cough"},
  {id: "111", question: "김", answer: "kim"},
  {id: "112", question: "김밥", answer: "kimbab"},
  {id: "113", question: "김치", answer: "kimchi"},
  {id: "114", question: "김치찌개", answer: "kimchi stew"},
  {id: "115", question: "깎다", answer: "cut"},
  {id: "116", question: "깨끗하다", answer: "clean"},
  {id: "117", question: "깻잎", answer: "sesame leaf"},
  {id: "118", question: "꼭", answer: "exactly"},
  {id: "119", question: "꽃", answer: "flower"},
  {id: "120", question: "꽃집", answer: "flower shop"},
  {id: "121", question: "꿀", answer: "honey"},
  {id: "122", question: "끄다", answer: "turn off"},
  {id: "123", question: "끓이다", answer: "boil"},
  {id: "124", question: "나가다", answer: "go out"},
  {id: "125", question: "나라", answer: "country"},
  {id: "126", question: "나쁘다", answer: "bad"},
  {id: "127", question: "나오다", answer: "come out"},
  {id: "128", question: "나이", answer: "age"},
  {id: "129", question: "나중", answer: "later"},
  {id: "130", question: "날", answer: "day"},
  {id: "131", question: "날씨", answer: "weather"},
  {id: "132", question: "날씬하다", answer: "slim"},
  {id: "133", question: "날짜", answer: "date"},
  {id: "134", question: "남동생", answer: "younger brother"},
  {id: "135", question: "남부 지방", answer: "southern region"},
  {id: "136", question: "남이섬", answer: "Nami Island"},
  {id: "137", question: "남자", answer: "man"},
  {id: "138", question: "남편", answer: "husband"},
  {id: "139", question: "낮", answer: "day"},
  {id: "140", question: "낮다", answer: "low"},
  {id: "141", question: "내과", answer: "internal medicine"},
  {id: "142", question: "내년", answer: "next year"},
  {id: "143", question: "내려가다", answer: "go down"},
  {id: "144", question: "내일", answer: "tomorrow"},
  {id: "145", question: "냉면", answer: "cold noodles"},
  {id: "146", question: "냉장고", answer: "refrigerator"},
  {id: "147", question: "너무", answer: "too"},
  {id: "148", question: "넓다", answer: "to be wide"},
  {id: "149", question: "넘어지다", answer: "fall down"},
  {id: "150", question: "넣다", answer: "to insert"},
  {id: "151", question: "넥타이", answer: "necktie"},
  {id: "152", question: "노래", answer: "song"},
  {id: "153", question: "노래방", answer: "karaoke"},
  {id: "154", question: "놀다", answer: "to play"},
  {id: "155", question: "놀이공원", answer: "amusement park"},
  {id: "156", question: "농구", answer: "basketball"},
  {id: "157", question: "농구공", answer: "a basketball"},
  {id: "158", question: "농부", answer: "farmer"},
  {id: "159", question: "높다", answer: "high"},
  {id: "160", question: "누가", answer: "who"},
  {id: "161", question: "누구", answer: "who"},
  {id: "162", question: "누나", answer: "sister"},
  {id: "163", question: "눈", answer: "eye"},
  {id: "164", question: "눈병", answer: "eye disease"},
  {id: "165", question: "느리다", answer: "slow"},
  {id: "166", question: "늦다", answer: "be late"},
  {id: "167", question: "다니다", answer: "attend"},
  {id: "168", question: "다리", answer: "bridge"},
  {id: "169", question: "다리", answer: "leg"},
  {id: "170", question: "다섯", answer: "five"},
  {id: "171", question: "다시", answer: "again"},
  {id: "172", question: "다용도실", answer: "utility room"},
  {id: "173", question: "다음 달", answer: "next month"},
  {id: "174", question: "다음 주", answer: "next week"},
  {id: "175", question: "다치다", answer: "get hurt"},
  {id: "176", question: "단오", answer: "Korean Spring Festival"},
  {id: "177", question: "단풍", answer: "foliage"},
  {id: "178", question: "달력", answer: "calendar"},
  {id: "179", question: "닭", answer: "chicken"},
  {id: "180", question: "닭갈비", answer: "chicken ribs"},
  {id: "181", question: "담배를 피우다", answer: "smoke a cigarette"},
  {id: "182", question: "당근", answer: "carrot"},
  {id: "183", question: "대", answer: "versus"},
  {id: "184", question: "대추", answer: "jujube"},
  {id: "185", question: "대추차", answer: "jujube tea"},
  {id: "186", question: "대학생", answer: "college student"},
  {id: "187", question: "댁", answer: "house"},
  {id: "188", question: "더", answer: "more"},
  {id: "189", question: "덥다", answer: "hot"},
  {id: "190", question: "도서관", answer: "library"},
  {id: "191", question: "도시", answer: "city"},
  {id: "192", question: "도장", answer: "stamp"},
  {id: "193", question: "도착하다", answer: "arrive"},
  {id: "194", question: "돈", answer: "money"},
  {id: "195", question: "돈가스", answer: "pork cutlets"},
  {id: "196", question: "돈을 넣다", answer: "put the money"},
  {id: "197", question: "돈을 보내다", answer: "spend your money"},
  {id: "198", question: "돈을 찾다", answer: "withdraw cash"},
  {id: "199", question: "돌", answer: "stone"},
  {id: "200", question: "돌아오다", answer: "come back"},
  {id: "201", question: "돌잔치", answer: "birthday party"},
  {id: "202", question: "돌잡이", answer: "Doljabi"},
  {id: "203", question: "돕다", answer: "help"},
  {id: "204", question: "동료", answer: "colleague"},
  {id: "205", question: "동안", answer: "during"},
  {id: "206", question: "동전", answer: "coin"},
  {id: "207", question: "동주민센터", answer: "east community center"},
  {id: "208", question: "동화책", answer: "fairy tale book"},
  {id: "209", question: "돼지", answer: "pig"},
  {id: "210", question: "돼지고기", answer: "pork"},
  {id: "211", question: "된장", answer: "bean paste"},
  {id: "212", question: "된장찌개", answer: "bean paste stew"},
  {id: "213", question: "두부", answer: "tofu"},
  {id: "214", question: "두통", answer: "headache"},
  {id: "215", question: "뒤", answer: "rear"},
  {id: "216", question: "드라마", answer: "drama"},
  {id: "217", question: "드리다", answer: "give"},
  {id: "218", question: "드시다", answer: "eat"},
  {id: "219", question: "들어가다", answer: "go in"},
  {id: "220", question: "등산", answer: "mountain climbing"},
  {id: "221", question: "등산화", answer: "hiking boots"},
  {id: "222", question: "따뜻하다", answer: "warm"},
  {id: "223", question: "딸", answer: "daughter"},
  {id: "224", question: "딸기", answer: "strawberry"},
  {id: "225", question: "떠들다", answer: "be noisy"},
  {id: "226", question: "떡국", answer: "rice cake soup"},
  {id: "227", question: "떡볶이", answer: "rice cake stirfry"},
  {id: "228", question: "똑똑하다", answer: "smart"},
  {id: "229", question: "뚱뚱하다", answer: "fat"},
  {id: "230", question: "뜨겁다", answer: "hot"},
  {id: "231", question: "뜻", answer: "meaning"},
  {id: "232", question: "띠", answer: "zodiac sign"},
  {id: "233", question: "라면", answer: "ramen"},
  {id: "234", question: "린스", answer: "conditioner"},
  {id: "235", question: "마당", answer: "yard (place)"},
  {id: "236", question: "마리", answer: "animal (counter)"},
  {id: "237", question: "마시다", answer: "drink"},
  {id: "238", question: "마트", answer: "mart"},
  {id: "239", question: "만나다", answer: "meet"},
  {id: "240", question: "만나서 반갑습니다", answer: "nice to meet you"},
  {id: "241", question: "만지다", answer: "to touch"},
  {id: "242", question: "많다", answer: "to have a lot [of]"},
  {id: "243", question: "많이", answer: "a lot of"},
  {id: "244", question: "말", answer: "horse"},
  {id: "245", question: "맛있게 드세요", answer: "bon appetit"},
  {id: "246", question: "맛있다", answer: "to be delicious"},
  {id: "247", question: "맞다", answer: "right"},
  {id: "248", question: "매실", answer: "plum"},
  {id: "249", question: "매일", answer: "everyday"},
  {id: "250", question: "맥주", answer: "beer"},
  {id: "251", question: "맵다", answer: "spicy"},
  {id: "252", question: "머리", answer: "head"},
  {id: "253", question: "머리핀", answer: "hair pin"},
  {id: "254", question: "먹다", answer: "eat"},
  {id: "255", question: "먼저", answer: "first"},
  {id: "256", question: "멀다", answer: "to be far"},
  {id: "257", question: "멋있다", answer: "to be stylish"},
  {id: "258", question: "멍이 들다", answer: "get bruises"},
  {id: "259", question: "명", answer: "persons"},
  {id: "260", question: "명절", answer: "holiday"},
  {id: "261", question: "모과차", answer: "quince tea"},
  {id: "262", question: "모두", answer: "all"},
  {id: "263", question: "모레", answer: "day after tomorrow"},
  {id: "264", question: "모르다", answer: "to not know"},
  {id: "265", question: "모이다", answer: "gather"},
  {id: "266", question: "모자", answer: "hat"},
  {id: "267", question: "목", answer: "neck"},
  {id: "268", question: "목걸이", answer: "necklace"},
  {id: "269", question: "목소리", answer: "voice"},
  {id: "270", question: "목요일", answer: "Thursday"},
  {id: "271", question: "몸살", answer: "ache"},
  {id: "272", question: "몽골", answer: "Mongolia"},
  {id: "273", question: "무", answer: "radish"},
  {id: "274", question: "무궁화", answer: "rose of sharon"},
  {id: "275", question: "무릎", answer: "knee"},
  {id: "276", question: "무리하다", answer: "overwork"},
  {id: "277", question: "무슨", answer: "what kind"},
  {id: "278", question: "무엇", answer: "what"},
  {id: "279", question: "문", answer: "door"},
  {id: "280", question: "문화", answer: "culture"},
  {id: "281", question: "물", answer: "water"},
  {id: "282", question: "물약", answer: "liquid medicine"},
  {id: "283", question: "물파스", answer: "Liquid Pas"},
  {id: "284", question: "미안합니다", answer: "sorry"},
  {id: "285", question: "미역국", answer: "seaweed soup"},
  {id: "286", question: "미용사", answer: "hairdresser"},
  {id: "287", question: "미용실", answer: "salon"},
  {id: "288", question: "바나나", answer: "banana"},
  {id: "289", question: "바쁘다", answer: "busy"},
  {id: "290", question: "바지", answer: "pants"},
  {id: "291", question: "박물관", answer: "museum"},
  {id: "292", question: "밖", answer: "out"},
  {id: "293", question: "반", answer: "half"},
  {id: "294", question: "반창고", answer: "bandaid"},
  {id: "295", question: "받다", answer: "receive"},
  {id: "296", question: "발", answer: "foot"},
  {id: "297", question: "밤(과일)", answer: "chestnut"},
  {id: "298", question: "밤(시간)", answer: "night"},
  {id: "299", question: "밥", answer: "rice"},
  {id: "300", question: "방", answer: "room"},
  {id: "301", question: "방법", answer: "method"},
  {id: "302", question: "배(과일)", answer: "pear"},
  {id: "303", question: "배(교통수단)", answer: "boat"},
  {id: "304", question: "배낭", answer: "backpack"},
  {id: "305", question: "배달", answer: "delivery"},
  {id: "306", question: "배달하다", answer: "to deliver"},
  {id: "307", question: "배우", answer: "actor"},
  {id: "308", question: "배우다", answer: "to learn"},
  {id: "309", question: "배추", answer: "cabbage"},
  {id: "310", question: "배탈이 나다", answer: "have a stomachache"},
  {id: "311", question: "백두산", answer: "Baekdu Mountain"},
  {id: "312", question: "백일", answer: "one hundred days"},
  {id: "313", question: "백화점", answer: "department store"},
  {id: "314", question: "밴드", answer: "band"},
  {id: "315", question: "밴드를 붙이다", answer: "put on a bandaid"},
  {id: "316", question: "뱀", answer: "snake"},
  {id: "317", question: "버리다", answer: "throw away"},
  {id: "318", question: "버섯", answer: "mushroom"},
  {id: "319", question: "버스터미널", answer: "bus terminal"},
  {id: "320", question: "번역가", answer: "translator"},
  {id: "321", question: "벌", answer: "bee"},
  {id: "322", question: "베란다", answer: "veranda"},
  {id: "323", question: "베트남", answer: "Vietnam"},
  {id: "324", question: "벨트", answer: "belt"},
  {id: "325", question: "변기", answer: "toilet"},
  {id: "326", question: "변호사", answer: "lawyer"},
  {id: "327", question: "병(단위명사)", answer: "bottle"},
  {id: "328", question: "병원", answer: "hospital"},
  {id: "329", question: "보건소", answer: "health center"},
  {id: "330", question: "보내다", answer: "send"},
  {id: "331", question: "보다", answer: "see"},
  {id: "332", question: "보름달", answer: "full moon"},
  {id: "333", question: "보쌈", answer: "bossam"},
  {id: "334", question: "보통", answer: "usually"},
  {id: "335", question: "보통이다", answer: "to be normal"},
  {id: "336", question: "복숭아", answer: "peach"},
  {id: "337", question: "볶음밥", answer: "fried rice"},
  {id: "338", question: "볼펜", answer: "pen"},
  {id: "339", question: "봄", answer: "spring"},
  {id: "340", question: "부러지다", answer: "to break"},
  {id: "341", question: "부르다", answer: "call"},
  {id: "342", question: "부모님", answer: "parents"},
  {id: "343", question: "부부", answer: "couple"},
  {id: "344", question: "부산", answer: "Busan"},
  {id: "345", question: "부엌", answer: "kitchen"},
  {id: "346", question: "부지런하다", answer: "be diligent"},
  {id: "347", question: "부채춤", answer: "fan dance"},
  {id: "348", question: "부츠", answer: "boots"},
  {id: "349", question: "분 (시간)", answer: "minute"},
  {id: "350", question: "분 (높은 말)", answer: "person"},
  {id: "351", question: "분식", answer: "flour-based food"},
  {id: "352", question: "분식집", answer: "Korean snack stand"},
  {id: "353", question: "불고기", answer: "bulgogi"},
  {id: "354", question: "불다", answer: "to blow"},
  {id: "355", question: "붙이다", answer: "to attach"},
  {id: "356", question: "블라우스", answer: "blouse"},
  {id: "357", question: "비", answer: "rain"},
  {id: "358", question: "비밀번호", answer: "password"},
  {id: "359", question: "비빔밥", answer: "bibimbap"},
  {id: "360", question: "비싸다", answer: "expensive"},
  {id: "361", question: "비자", answer: "visa"},
  {id: "362", question: "비타민", answer: "vitamin"},
  {id: "363", question: "비행기", answer: "airplane"},
  {id: "364", question: "빠르다", answer: "fast"},
  {id: "365", question: "빨래", answer: "laundry"},
  {id: "366", question: "빨리", answer: "quickly"},
  {id: "367", question: "빵", answer: "bread"},
  {id: "368", question: "빵집", answer: "bakery"},
  {id: "369", question: "사과", answer: "apple"},
  {id: "370", question: "사다", answer: "buy"},
  {id: "371", question: "사람", answer: "person"},
  {id: "372", question: "사랑하다", answer: "love"},
  {id: "373", question: "사무실", answer: "office"},
  {id: "374", question: "사업가", answer: "entrepreneur"},
  {id: "375", question: "사이", answer: "between"},
  {id: "376", question: "사장님", answer: "boss"},
  {id: "377", question: "사전", answer: "dictionary"},
  {id: "378", question: "사진", answer: "photo"},
  {id: "379", question: "사진을 찍다", answer: "take pictures"},
  {id: "380", question: "산부인과", answer: "obstetrics & gynecology"},
  {id: "381", question: "살다", answer: "live"},
  {id: "382", question: "삼겹살", answer: "pork belly"},
  {id: "383", question: "삼계탕", answer: "chicken and ginseng soup"},
  {id: "384", question: "삼촌", answer: "uncle"},
  {id: "385", question: "상설할인매장", answer: "permanent discount stores"},
  {id: "386", question: "상자", answer: "box"},
  {id: "387", question: "상처", answer: "wound"},
  {id: "388", question: "상추", answer: "lettuce"},
  {id: "389", question: "샌들", answer: "sandal"},
  {id: "390", question: "생강차", answer: "ginger tea"},
  {id: "391", question: "생선", answer: "fish"},
  {id: "392", question: "생신", answer: "birthday"},
  {id: "393", question: "생일", answer: "birthday"},
  {id: "394", question: "생활", answer: "life"},
  {id: "395", question: "생활용품", answer: "household goods"},
  {id: "396", question: "샤브샤브", answer: "shabu"},
  {id: "397", question: "샴푸", answer: "shampoo"},
  {id: "398", question: "서명", answer: "signature"},
  {id: "399", question: "서울", answer: "Seoul"},
  {id: "400", question: "서점", answer: "bookstore"},
  {id: "401", question: "석류", answer: "pomegranate"},
  {id: "402", question: "선글라스", answer: "sunglasses"},
  {id: "403", question: "선물", answer: "gift"},
  {id: "404", question: "선생님", answer: "teacher"},
  {id: "405", question: "설날", answer: "new year"},
  {id: "406", question: "설사", answer: "diarrhea"},
  {id: "407", question: "설악산", answer: "Mt. Seorak"},
  {id: "408", question: "성격", answer: "character"},
  {id: "409", question: "성격이 좋다", answer: "good nature"},
  {id: "410", question: "성명", answer: "name"},
  {id: "411", question: "성묘를 하다", answer: "ancestor reverence"},
  {id: "412", question: "성함", answer: "name"},
  {id: "413", question: "세다", answer: "count"},
  {id: "414", question: "세면대", answer: "wash basin"},
  {id: "415", question: "세배를 하다", answer: "bow down (for New Years)"},
  {id: "416", question: "세종대왕", answer: "King Sejong"},
  {id: "417", question: "세탁기", answer: "laundry machine"},
  {id: "418", question: "세탁소", answer: "laundromat"},
  {id: "419", question: "센터", answer: "center"},
  {id: "420", question: "셔츠", answer: "shirt"},
  {id: "421", question: "소", answer: "ox"},
  {id: "422", question: "소개", answer: "introduce"},
  {id: "423", question: "소개하다", answer: "to introduce"},
  {id: "424", question: "소독약", answer: "antiseptic"},
  {id: "425", question: "소방관", answer: "firefighter"},
  {id: "426", question: "소방서", answer: "fire station"},
  {id: "427", question: "소원을 빌다", answer: "make a wish"},
  {id: "428", question: "소파", answer: "sofa"},
  {id: "429", question: "소포", answer: "parcel"},
  {id: "430", question: "소화제", answer: "digestive medicine"},
  {id: "431", question: "손", answer: "hand"},
  {id: "432", question: "손가락", answer: "finger"},
  {id: "433", question: "손님", answer: "customer"},
  {id: "434", question: "송이", answer: "bunch (of)"},
  {id: "435", question: "송편", answer: "songpyeon (rice cake)"},
  {id: "436", question: "송편을 빚다", answer: "make songpyeon"},
  {id: "437", question: "쇼핑", answer: "shopping"},
  {id: "438", question: "쇼핑하다", answer: "to shop"},
  {id: "439", question: "수건", answer: "towel"},
  {id: "440", question: "수도", answer: "question"},
  {id: "441", question: "수령", answer: "receipt"},
  {id: "442", question: "수박", answer: "watermelon"},
  {id: "443", question: "수업", answer: "class"},
  {id: "444", question: "수영", answer: "swimming"},
  {id: "445", question: "수영장", answer: "swimming pool"},
  {id: "446", question: "수요일", answer: "Wednesday"},
  {id: "447", question: "수표", answer: "check"},
  {id: "448", question: "숙소", answer: "rooms"},
  {id: "449", question: "숙제", answer: "homework"},
  {id: "450", question: "숙제하다", answer: "do homework"},
  {id: "451", question: "순두부찌개", answer: "tofu stew"},
  {id: "452", question: "숫자", answer: "number"},
  {id: "453", question: "쉬다", answer: "rest"},
  {id: "454", question: "슈퍼마켓", answer: "supermarket"},
  {id: "455", question: "스웨터", answer: "sweater"},
  {id: "456", question: "스카프", answer: "scarf"},
  {id: "457", question: "슬리퍼", answer: "slipper"},
  {id: "458", question: "시간", answer: "time"},
  {id: "459", question: "시계", answer: "clock"},
  {id: "460", question: "시골", answer: "country"},
  {id: "461", question: "시금치", answer: "spinach"},
  {id: "462", question: "시끄럽다", answer: "be noisy"},
  {id: "463", question: "시원하다", answer: "be cool"},
  {id: "464", question: "시작하다", answer: "to start"},
  {id: "465", question: "시장", answer: "market"},
  {id: "466", question: "시청", answer: "city hall"},
  {id: "467", question: "시키다", answer: "force somebody to do"},
  {id: "468", question: "식당", answer: "restaurant"},
  {id: "469", question: "식물원", answer: "botanical garden"},
  {id: "470", question: "식용유", answer: "cooking oil"},
  {id: "471", question: "식탁", answer: "table"},
  {id: "472", question: "식후", answer: "after a meal"},
  {id: "473", question: "신문", answer: "newspaper"},
  {id: "474", question: "신발", answer: "shoes"},
  {id: "475", question: "신분증", answer: "identification"},
  {id: "476", question: "신청서", answer: "application"},
  {id: "477", question: "실례합니다", answer: "excuse me"},
  {id: "478", question: "싫어하다", answer: "dislike"},
  {id: "479", question: "싸다", answer: "cheap"},
  {id: "480", question: "쌀국수", answer: "rice noodles"},
  {id: "481", question: "씨름을 하다", answer: "wrestle"},
  {id: "482", question: "씻다", answer: "wash"},
  {id: "483", question: "아기를 낳다", answer: "give birth"},
  {id: "484", question: "아내", answer: "wife"},
  {id: "485", question: "아니에요", answer: "no"},
  {id: "486", question: "아들", answer: "son"},
  {id: "487", question: "아래", answer: "bottom"},
  {id: "488", question: "아리랑", answer: "arirang"},
  {id: "489", question: "아마", answer: "maybe"},
  {id: "490", question: "아이", answer: "children"},
  {id: "491", question: "아이스크림", answer: "ice cream"},
  {id: "492", question: "아저씨", answer: "mister"},
  {id: "493", question: "아주", answer: "very"},
  {id: "494", question: "아주머니", answer: "old lady"},
  {id: "495", question: "아직", answer: "yet"},
  {id: "496", question: "아침", answer: "morning"},
  {id: "497", question: "아파트", answer: "apartment"},
  {id: "498", question: "아프다", answer: "pain"},
  {id: "499", question: "안", answer: "within"},
  {id: "500", question: "안경을 끼다", answer: "wear glasses"},
  {id: "501", question: "안과", answer: "ophthalmology"},
  {id: "502", question: "안녕?", answer: "hey"},
  {id: "503", question: "안녕하세요", answer: "hello"},
  {id: "504", question: "안녕히 가세요", answer: "please go well"},
  {id: "505", question: "안녕히 계세요", answer: "please stay well"},
  {id: "506", question: "안녕히 주무세요", answer: "good night"},
  {id: "507", question: "안녕히 주무셨어요?", answer: "good morning"},
  {id: "508", question: "안약을 넣다", answer: "apply eye drops"},
  {id: "509", question: "앉다", answer: "sit"},
  {id: "510", question: "알다", answer: "know"},
  {id: "511", question: "알약", answer: "pill"},
  {id: "512", question: "앞", answer: "front"},
  {id: "513", question: "애국가", answer: "national anthem"},
  {id: "514", question: "액세서리", answer: "accessory"},
  {id: "515", question: "야구", answer: "baseball"},
  {id: "516", question: "야구공", answer: "a baseball"},
  {id: "517", question: "야식", answer: "late night meal"},
  {id: "518", question: "약", answer: "medicine"},
  {id: "519", question: "약국", answer: "pharmacy"},
  {id: "520", question: "약속", answer: "appointment"},
  {id: "521", question: "양", answer: "sheep"},
  {id: "522", question: "양념 치킨", answer: "marinated chicken"},
  {id: "523", question: "양말", answer: "socks"},
  {id: "524", question: "양배추", answer: "cabbage"},
  {id: "525", question: "양복", answer: "suit"},
  {id: "526", question: "양식", answer: "Western food"},
  {id: "527", question: "양파", answer: "onion"},
  {id: "528", question: "어깨", answer: "shoulder"},
  {id: "529", question: "어디", answer: "where"},
  {id: "530", question: "어디에 살아요?", answer: "where do you live?"},
  {id: "531", question: "어디에서 왔어요?", answer: "where are you from?"},
  {id: "532", question: "어제", answer: "yesterday"},
  {id: "533", question: "언니", answer: "sister"},
  {id: "534", question: "언제", answer: "when"},
  {id: "535", question: "얼굴", answer: "face"},
  {id: "536", question: "얼마나 걸려요?", answer: "how long does it take?"},
  {id: "537", question: "없다", answer: "be nonexistent"},
  {id: "538", question: "에스컬레이터", answer: "escalator"},
  {id: "539", question: "에어컨", answer: "air conditioner"},
  {id: "540", question: "엘리베이터", answer: "elevator"},
  {id: "541", question: "여권", answer: "passport"},
  {id: "542", question: "여기", answer: "here"},
  {id: "543", question: "여동생", answer: "younger sister"},
  {id: "544", question: "여름", answer: "summer"},
  {id: "545", question: "여보", answer: "darling"},
  {id: "546", question: "여자", answer: "woman"},
  {id: "547", question: "여행사", answer: "travel agency"},
  {id: "548", question: "역", answer: "station"},
  {id: "549", question: "연고", answer: "ointment"},
  {id: "550", question: "연락하다", answer: "contact"},
  {id: "551", question: "연세", answer: "age"},
  {id: "552", question: "연장하다", answer: "extend"},
  {id: "553", question: "연필", answer: "pencil"},
  {id: "554", question: "연휴", answer: "holidays"},
  {id: "555", question: "열", answer: "ten"},
  {id: "556", question: "열다", answer: "open"},
  {id: "557", question: "열쇠", answer: "key"},
  {id: "558", question: "열심히", answer: "hard"},
  {id: "559", question: "열이 나다", answer: "have a fever"},
  {id: "560", question: "영어", answer: "English"},
  {id: "561", question: "영화", answer: "movie"},
  {id: "562", question: "영화관", answer: "cinema"},
  {id: "563", question: "영화를 보다", answer: "watch a movie"},
  {id: "564", question: "옆", answer: "side"},
  {id: "565", question: "예쁘다", answer: "be pretty"},
  {id: "566", question: "예약하다", answer: "make a reservation"},
  {id: "567", question: "오늘", answer: "today"},
  {id: "568", question: "오다", answer: "come"},
  {id: "569", question: "오렌지", answer: "orange"},
  {id: "570", question: "오른쪽", answer: "right"},
  {id: "571", question: "오빠", answer: "brother"},
  {id: "572", question: "오이", answer: "cucumber"},
  {id: "573", question: "오전", answer: "morning"},
  {id: "574", question: "오후", answer: "afternoon"},
  {id: "575", question: "올라가다", answer: "go up"},
  {id: "576", question: "올해", answer: "this year"},
  {id: "577", question: "옷", answer: "dress"},
  {id: "578", question: "옷장", answer: "closet"},
  {id: "579", question: "외국인등록증", answer: "alien registration card"},
  {id: "580", question: "외모", answer: "appearance"},
  {id: "581", question: "외삼촌", answer: "maternal uncle"},
  {id: "582", question: "외할머니", answer: "maternal grandmother"},
  {id: "583", question: "외할아버지", answer: "maternal grandfather"},
  {id: "584", question: "왼쪽", answer: "left"},
  {id: "585", question: "요가", answer: "yoga"},
  {id: "586", question: "요리", answer: "cooking"},
  {id: "587", question: "요리사", answer: "a cook"},
  {id: "588", question: "요리하다", answer: "to cook"},
  {id: "589", question: "요일", answer: "day of the week"},
  {id: "590", question: "요즘", answer: "nowadays"},
  {id: "591", question: "욕실", answer: "bathroom"},
  {id: "592", question: "욕조", answer: "tub"},
  {id: "593", question: "용", answer: "dragon"},
  {id: "594", question: "우리", answer: "us"},
  {id: "595", question: "우산", answer: "umbrella"},
  {id: "596", question: "우유", answer: "milk"},
  {id: "597", question: "우체국", answer: "post office"},
  {id: "598", question: "우체통", answer: "mailbox"},
  {id: "599", question: "우표", answer: "stamp"},
  {id: "600", question: "운동", answer: "exercise"},
  {id: "601", question: "운동선수", answer: "athlete"},
  {id: "602", question: "운동장", answer: "playground"},
  {id: "603", question: "운동하다", answer: "to exercise"},
  {id: "604", question: "운동화", answer: "running shoes"},
  {id: "605", question: "운전기사", answer: "chauffeur"},
  {id: "606", question: "운전면허증", answer: "driver's license"},
  {id: "607", question: "울다", answer: "to cry"},
  {id: "608", question: "웃다", answer: "to laugh"},
  {id: "609", question: "원숭이", answer: "monkey"},
  {id: "610", question: "원피스", answer: "dress"},
  {id: "611", question: "월요일", answer: "Monday"},
  {id: "612", question: "위", answer: "top"},
  {id: "613", question: "윷놀이", answer: "Korean board game"},
  {id: "614", question: "은행", answer: "bank"},
  {id: "615", question: "음력", answer: "lunar calendar"},
  {id: "616", question: "음식", answer: "food"},
  {id: "617", question: "의료보험증", answer: "health insurance"},
  {id: "618", question: "의사", answer: "doctor"},
  {id: "619", question: "의자", answer: "chair"},
  {id: "620", question: "이", answer: "this"},
  {id: "621", question: "이렇게", answer: "like this"},
  {id: "622", question: "이를 닦다", answer: "brush teeth"},
  {id: "623", question: "이름", answer: "name"},
  {id: "624", question: "이름이 뭐예요?", answer: "what's your name?"},
  {id: "625", question: "이마", answer: "forehead"},
  {id: "626", question: "이메일", answer: "e-mail"},
  {id: "627", question: "이모", answer: "aunt"},
  {id: "628", question: "이모티콘", answer: "emoticon"},
  {id: "629", question: "이번 달", answer: "this month"},
  {id: "630", question: "이번 주", answer: "this week"},
  {id: "631", question: "이야기", answer: "story"},
  {id: "632", question: "이쪽", answer: "this way"},
  {id: "633", question: "인분", answer: "serving (per person)"},
  {id: "634", question: "인사", answer: "greetings"},
  {id: "635", question: "인사동", answer: "Insa-dong"},
  {id: "636", question: "인삼", answer: "ginseng"},
  {id: "637", question: "인터넷 쇼핑", answer: "online shopping"},
  {id: "638", question: "일과", answer: "daily routine"},
  {id: "639", question: "일본", answer: "Japan"},
  {id: "640", question: "일식", answer: "Japanese food"},
  {id: "641", question: "일어나다", answer: "to rise"},
  {id: "642", question: "일요일", answer: "Sunday"},
  {id: "643", question: "일찍", answer: "early"},
  {id: "644", question: "일하다", answer: "work"},
  {id: "645", question: "읽다", answer: "read"},
  {id: "646", question: "입", answer: "mouth"},
  {id: "647", question: "입학하다", answer: "enter a school"},
  {id: "648", question: "있다", answer: "have"},
  {id: "649", question: "자다", answer: "sleep"},
  {id: "650", question: "자동차", answer: "car"},
  {id: "651", question: "자장면", answer: "noodles"},
  {id: "652", question: "자전거", answer: "bicycle"},
  {id: "653", question: "자주", answer: "often"},
  {id: "654", question: "작년", answer: "last year"},
  {id: "655", question: "작다", answer: "small"},
  {id: "656", question: "잔", answer: "glass"},
  {id: "657", question: "잔치", answer: "party"},
  {id: "658", question: "잘 먹겠습니다", answer: "I will enjoy this food"},
  {id: "659", question: "잘생기다", answer: "be handsome"},
  {id: "660", question: "잡채", answer: "japchae"},
  {id: "661", question: "잣", answer: "pine nuts"},
  {id: "662", question: "장", answer: "sheet (counter)"},
  {id: "663", question: "장보기", answer: "shopping"},
  {id: "664", question: "장소", answer: "place"},
  {id: "665", question: "재료", answer: "material"},
  {id: "666", question: "재미있다", answer: "be interesting"},
  {id: "667", question: "저", answer: "that"},
  {id: "668", question: "저(제)", answer: "I, me, mine"},
  {id: "669", question: "저기", answer: "there"},
  {id: "670", question: "저녁", answer: "dinner"},
  {id: "671", question: "저쪽", answer: "there"},
  {id: "672", question: "적다", answer: "little"},
  {id: "673", question: "전자사전", answer: "electronic dictionary"},
  {id: "674", question: "전자상가", answer: "electronics store"},
  {id: "675", question: "전화", answer: "telephone"},
  {id: "676", question: "전화를 걸다", answer: "to call by phone"},
  {id: "677", question: "전화를 끊다", answer: "hang up the phone"},
  {id: "678", question: "전화를 바꾸다", answer: "put sb else on phone"},
  {id: "679", question: "전화를 받다", answer: "receive a call"},
  {id: "680", question: "전화번호", answer: "phone number"},
  {id: "681", question: "전화번호가 몇 번이에요?", answer: "what's your phone number?"},
  {id: "682", question: "전화하다", answer: "make a phone call"},
  {id: "683", question: "점심", answer: "lunch"},
  {id: "684", question: "점퍼", answer: "jacket"},
  {id: "685", question: "정류장", answer: "station, stop"},
  {id: "686", question: "정말", answer: "really"},
  {id: "687", question: "정원", answer: "garden"},
  {id: "688", question: "정장", answer: "formal dress"},
  {id: "689", question: "정형외과", answer: "orthopedics"},
  {id: "690", question: "제목", answer: "title"},
  {id: "691", question: "제주도", answer: "Jeju Island"},
  {id: "692", question: "조금", answer: "a little"},
  {id: "693", question: "조끼", answer: "vest"},
  {id: "694", question: "조심하다", answer: "be careful"},
  {id: "695", question: "조용하다", answer: "be silent"},
  {id: "696", question: "족발", answer: "pig's feet"},
  {id: "697", question: "좋다", answer: "be good"},
  {id: "698", question: "좋아하다", answer: "to like"},
  {id: "699", question: "죄송합니다", answer: "sorry"},
  {id: "700", question: "주다", answer: "give"},
  {id: "701", question: "주말", answer: "weekend"},
  {id: "702", question: "주머니", answer: "pocket"},
  {id: "703", question: "주무시다", answer: "to sleep"},
  {id: "704", question: "주문", answer: "order"},
  {id: "705", question: "주문하다", answer: "place an order"},
  {id: "706", question: "주민등록등본", answer: "copy of ID card"},
  {id: "707", question: "주민등록증", answer: "ID card"},
  {id: "708", question: "주민센터", answer: "community center"},
  {id: "709", question: "주방", answer: "kitchen"},
  {id: "710", question: "주부", answer: "housewife"},
  {id: "711", question: "주사를 맞다", answer: "get a shot (med)"},
  {id: "712", question: "주스", answer: "juice"},
  {id: "713", question: "주차장", answer: "parking lot"},
  {id: "714", question: "주차하다", answer: "to park a car"},
  {id: "715", question: "준비하다", answer: "prepare"},
  {id: "716", question: "중국", answer: "China"},
  {id: "717", question: "중국어", answer: "Chinese"},
  {id: "718", question: "중국집", answer: "Chinese restaurant"},
  {id: "719", question: "중부 지방", answer: "Central Region"},
  {id: "720", question: "중식", answer: "Chinese food"},
  {id: "721", question: "쥐", answer: "rat"},
  {id: "722", question: "즐겁다", answer: "be enjoyable"},
  {id: "723", question: "지갑", answer: "wallet"},
  {id: "724", question: "지금", answer: "now"},
  {id: "725", question: "지난달", answer: "last month"},
  {id: "726", question: "지난주", answer: "last week"},
  {id: "727", question: "지우개", answer: "eraser"},
  {id: "728", question: "지폐", answer: "paper money"},
  {id: "729", question: "지하", answer: "underground"},
  {id: "730", question: "지하철역", answer: "subway station"},
  {id: "731", question: "직업", answer: "job"},
  {id: "732", question: "직원", answer: "employee"},
  {id: "733", question: "진지", answer: "serious"},
  {id: "734", question: "진통제", answer: "painkiller"},
  {id: "735", question: "집", answer: "house"},
  {id: "736", question: "집들이", answer: "housewarming"},
  {id: "737", question: "집안일", answer: "housework"},
  {id: "738", question: "차", answer: "car"},
  {id: "739", question: "차가 막히다", answer: "have a traffic jam"},
  {id: "740", question: "차례를 지내다", answer: "hold ancestral rites"},
  {id: "741", question: "차이", answer: "difference"},
  {id: "742", question: "착하다", answer: "be kind"},
  {id: "743", question: "참외", answer: "Korean melon"},
  {id: "744", question: "창고", answer: "warehouse"},
  {id: "745", question: "창문", answer: "window"},
  {id: "746", question: "찾다", answer: "find"},
  {id: "747", question: "채소", answer: "vegetable"},
  {id: "748", question: "책", answer: "book"},
  {id: "749", question: "책상", answer: "desk"},
  {id: "750", question: "처방전", answer: "prescription"},
  {id: "751", question: "청바지", answer: "blue jeans"},
  {id: "752", question: "청소", answer: "cleaning"},
  {id: "753", question: "청소하다", answer: "sweep"},
  {id: "754", question: "체격이 좋다", answer: "good physique"},
  {id: "755", question: "초대를 받다", answer: "receive an invitation"},
  {id: "756", question: "초대하다", answer: "invite"},
  {id: "757", question: "초등학교", answer: "elementary school"},
  {id: "758", question: "초밥", answer: "sushi"},
  {id: "759", question: "추다", answer: "dance"},
  {id: "760", question: "추석", answer: "thanksgiving"},
  {id: "761", question: "축구", answer: "soccer"},
  {id: "762", question: "축하", answer: "celebration"},
  {id: "763", question: "축하하다", answer: "celebrate"},
  {id: "764", question: "출구", answer: "exit"},
  {id: "765", question: "출근하다", answer: "go to work"},
  {id: "766", question: "출입국관리사무소", answer: "immigration office"},
  {id: "767", question: "춤", answer: "dance"},
  {id: "768", question: "춥다", answer: "cold"},
  {id: "769", question: "취미", answer: "hobby"},
  {id: "770", question: "층", answer: "layer"},
  {id: "771", question: "치과", answer: "dentist"},
  {id: "772", question: "치마", answer: "skirt"},
  {id: "773", question: "치킨", answer: "chicken"},
  {id: "774", question: "친구", answer: "friend"},
  {id: "775", question: "친절하다", answer: "kind"},
  {id: "776", question: "친척", answer: "relative"},
  {id: "777", question: "칠순", answer: "seventieth"},
  {id: "778", question: "칠판", answer: "blackboard"},
  {id: "779", question: "침대", answer: "bed"},
  {id: "780", question: "카드", answer: "card"},
  {id: "781", question: "카디건", answer: "cardigan"},
  {id: "782", question: "칼국수", answer: "kalguksu"},
  {id: "783", question: "캄보디아", answer: "Cambodia"},
  {id: "784", question: "캐나다", answer: "Canada"},
  {id: "785", question: "커피", answer: "coffee"},
  {id: "786", question: "커피숍", answer: "coffee shop"},
  {id: "787", question: "컴퓨터", answer: "computer"},
  {id: "788", question: "컵", answer: "cup"},
  {id: "789", question: "케이크", answer: "cake"},
  {id: "790", question: "켤레", answer: "pair"},
  {id: "791", question: "코", answer: "nose"},
  {id: "792", question: "코트", answer: "coat"},
  {id: "793", question: "콜라", answer: "cola"},
  {id: "794", question: "콧물", answer: "snot"},
  {id: "795", question: "퀵서비스", answer: "quick-service"},
  {id: "796", question: "크다", answer: "big"},
  {id: "797", question: "큰아버지", answer: "father's older brother"},
  {id: "798", question: "타다", answer: "ride"},
  {id: "799", question: "탁자", answer: "table"},
  {id: "800", question: "탕수육", answer: "sweet and sour pork"},
  {id: "801", question: "태권도", answer: "taekwondo"},
  {id: "802", question: "태권도장", answer: "taekwondo chapter"},
  {id: "803", question: "태극기", answer: "Korean flag"},
  {id: "804", question: "태어나다", answer: "be born"},
  {id: "805", question: "택시", answer: "taxi"},
  {id: "806", question: "텔레비전", answer: "television"},
  {id: "807", question: "토끼", answer: "rabbit"},
  {id: "808", question: "토마토", answer: "tomato"},
  {id: "809", question: "토요일", answer: "Saturday"},
  {id: "810", question: "통", answer: "barrel"},
  {id: "811", question: "통역사", answer: "translator"},
  {id: "812", question: "통장", answer: "bank book"},
  {id: "813", question: "통통하다", answer: "chubby"},
  {id: "814", question: "통화 중이다", answer: "phone line is busy"},
  {id: "815", question: "퇴근하다", answer: "leave the office"},
  {id: "816", question: "특히", answer: "especially"},
  {id: "817", question: "틀다", answer: "turn on"},
  {id: "818", question: "티셔츠", answer: "t-shirt"},
  {id: "819", question: "파", answer: "scallion"},
  {id: "820", question: "파란색", answer: "blue"},
  {id: "821", question: "파스", answer: "Pas"},
  {id: "822", question: "파티", answer: "party"},
  {id: "823", question: "팔찌", answer: "bracelet"},
  {id: "824", question: "팝콘", answer: "popcorn"},
  {id: "825", question: "팥빙수", answer: "red bean shaved ice"},
  {id: "826", question: "패션디자이너", answer: "fashion designer"},
  {id: "827", question: "편리하다", answer: "be convenient"},
  {id: "828", question: "편의점", answer: "convenience store"},
  {id: "829", question: "편지", answer: "letter"},
  {id: "830", question: "포기", answer: "Chinese cabbage"},
  {id: "831", question: "포도", answer: "grape"},
  {id: "832", question: "표", answer: "ticket"},
  {id: "833", question: "표시하다", answer: "indicate"},
  {id: "834", question: "푹", answer: "well, deep, good"},
  {id: "835", question: "피가 나다", answer: "blood oozes"},
  {id: "836", question: "피곤하다", answer: "be tired"},
  {id: "837", question: "피다", answer: "to bloom"},
  {id: "838", question: "피망", answer: "bell pepper"},
  {id: "839", question: "피아노", answer: "piano"},
  {id: "840", question: "피자", answer: "pizza"},
  {id: "841", question: "필리핀", answer: "Philippines"},
  {id: "842", question: "필통", answer: "pencil case"},
  {id: "843", question: "하루", answer: "one day"},
  {id: "844", question: "하루 종일", answer: "all day"},
  {id: "845", question: "하지만", answer: "but"},
  {id: "846", question: "학교", answer: "school"},
  {id: "847", question: "학생", answer: "student"},
  {id: "848", question: "학원", answer: "academy"},
  {id: "849", question: "한과", answer: "Korean cookie"},
  {id: "850", question: "한국", answer: "Korea"},
  {id: "851", question: "한국어", answer: "Korean Language"},
  {id: "852", question: "한국어를 배우다", answer: "learn Korean"},
  {id: "853", question: "한국인", answer: "Korean person"},
  {id: "854", question: "한글", answer: "Hangul"},
  {id: "855", question: "한글날", answer: "Hangul Day"},
  {id: "856", question: "한꺼번에", answer: "at the same time"},
  {id: "857", question: "한라산", answer: "Mt. Halla"},
  {id: "858", question: "한복", answer: "traditional Korean clothing"},
  {id: "859", question: "한식", answer: "Korean food"},
  {id: "860", question: "한옥", answer: "Korean houses"},
  {id: "861", question: "한우", answer: "Korean beef"},
  {id: "862", question: "할머니", answer: "grandmother"},
  {id: "863", question: "할아버지", answer: "grandfather"},
  {id: "864", question: "항공", answer: "airline"},
  {id: "865", question: "항상", answer: "always"},
  {id: "866", question: "햄버거", answer: "hamburger"},
  {id: "867", question: "행정 구역", answer: "area"},
  {id: "868", question: "헬스클럽", answer: "health club"},
  {id: "869", question: "현관", answer: "entrance"},
  {id: "870", question: "현금", answer: "cash"},
  {id: "871", question: "형", answer: "brother"},
  {id: "872", question: "호두", answer: "walnut"},
  {id: "873", question: "호랑이", answer: "tiger"},
  {id: "874", question: "호박", answer: "pumpkin"},
  {id: "875", question: "호텔", answer: "hotel"},
  {id: "876", question: "혼자", answer: "alone"},
  {id: "877", question: "홈쇼핑", answer: "home shopping"},
  {id: "878", question: "홍삼", answer: "red ginseng"},
  {id: "879", question: "화가", answer: "artist"},
  {id: "880", question: "화요일", answer: "Tuesday"},
  {id: "881", question: "화장대", answer: "vanity"},
  {id: "882", question: "화장실", answer: "restroom"},
  {id: "883", question: "화장품", answer: "cosmetics"},
  {id: "884", question: "화폐", answer: "currency"},
  {id: "885", question: "환갑", answer: "sixtieth birthday"},
  {id: "886", question: "회", answer: "raw meat"},
  {id: "887", question: "회사", answer: "company"},
  {id: "888", question: "회사원", answer: "employee"},
  {id: "889", question: "회식하다", answer: "company dinner"},
  {id: "890", question: "회의하다", answer: "discuss"},
  {id: "891", question: "휴가", answer: "vacation"},
  {id: "892", question: "휴게실", answer: "rest area"},
  {id: "893", question: "휴대폰", answer: "cellphone"},
  {id: "894", question: "힘들다", answer: "be difficult"},
  {id: "895", question: "ATM기기", answer: "ATM"},
];

/* Create word bundles in db */
function writeWordsinDB(dbstore, dictionary){
  dictionary.forEach(entry => {
    dbstore.put({word: entry});
  });
}